威尔 · 森特斯: 让我们看看，解决方案3,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Let's see, solution 3,
关键词，自动化的艰苦工作，新。
the keyword that automates the hard work,
new.
好处，写得更快，我明白了。
Benefits, faster to write, I get it.
看看这些蓝色，那不再是我们写的了。
Look at all the blue,
that wasn't us writing anymore.
经常用于专业领域。
Often still used professionally.
其中很大一部分是这样的，但是我们会看到，解决方案4稍微改变了它。
And a big part of it is, but we'll see,
solution 4 changes it slightly.
问题---- 95% 的开发人员不知道它是如何在引擎盖下工作的。
Problems, 95% of developers have no
idea how it's working under the hood.
我认为因此失败的面试，有一点雇佣兵的动机去学习,
I think therefore fail interview, there's
a slightly mercenary motivation to learn,
因此不能一直调试和构建干净可靠的代码。
and therefore can't debug and build
clean and reliable code all the time.
这里还有一个小问题，这是设计,
Here's another little problem with it,
this is the design,
我会说，流不是流，这是一个不明智的设计举措。
I would say, flow not a flow,
it's a not smart design move.
这个用户创建一个函数，如果我运行它没有新的关键字,
That user create a function if I
ran it without the new keyword,
我在代码库里找到的。
I found it in the code base.
当我运行我的团队，我开始运行没有新的关键字。
And when I was running my team and
I started running without the new keyword.
对于物体中的六个物质，这个结果会是什么呢？
What would the this end up that I refer
to in order to six stuff in the object?
它会指向布莱登什么？
What would it point to Braden?
布雷顿: 全球化。
&gt;&gt; Braydon: The global.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 这个全球性的物体，虽然知道它很伟大，但是,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: The global object,
as know great as it and yet,
你可能会说，很明显我需要新的关键词，对吧？
you might say, well, it's kinda obvious
I need to have the new keyword, right?
所以我们要这么早就拿到这个。
So we're gonna get this so early.
这不是因为我可能有其他代码之前，这是甚至在那里。
It kind of isn't because I might have
other code before that this is even there.
我可能有一个函数声明我正在使用它,
I might have like a function
declared that I am using it,
这个函数可能就在这个函数内部。
that this might be inside
the function that this equals.
关键是我不知道当我看到这个函数时，它需要一个新的
The point is I do not know when I look
at that function that it requires a new
关键字来完成它的工作。
keyword in order to do its job.
这可能不是最明智的设计决策，对吧？
That is probably not the smartest
design decision, right?
你可能希望能够看到函数,
You probably tend to want to be able
to look at the function and go,
我知道这需要一个新的关键词来做任何有用的事情。
I know that that requires a new
key word to do anything useful.
所以开发者们互相帮助。
So developers helped each other out.
如果你能想象这种语言，如果它是一个函数
If you can imagine the language
where if it's going to be a function
要求是自动化的东西，你不会声明它的功能
that requires is going to automate stuff,
you wouldn't declare it with function you
构造函数是一个典型的术语
declare it with and
the constructor is a typical term for
任何创建对象的东西。
anything that creates
constructs an object.
但是 JavaScript 没有做到这一点。
But JavaScript didn't do that.
他们说，没有问题是功能，留下它作为常规功能。
They said no problem is functions,
leaving it as regular function.
然后在运行函数时预先插入三个 new 字母。
And then insert three letters beforehand
new when you run the function.
我不知道。
I don't know.
这可不是什么好主意
That's not ideal for
你的团队成员喜欢，如果你写评论告诉他们，但。
your team members who are like if
you write comments to tell them but.
那么，开发人员在短时间内做了什么来互相帮助呢
So what did developers in a short
hand do to help each other out so
他们知道当他们看到一个函数，它需要一个新的关键字
that they know when they see a function
that it needs a new keyword in
为了完成它的工作？
front of it in order to do it's job?
好的，说吧，亚当。
Yeah, go ahead Adam.
亚当: 大写。
&gt;&gt; Adam: Capitalize.
威尔 · 句子: 第一个字母大写。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Capitalize
the first letter.
这就是为什么你不会看到，当你看到一个新的关键字被使用在前面
And that's why you won't see, whenever you
see a new keyword being used in front of
这个函数有一个大写字母。
a function the function
will have an upper case.
它没有任何意义，对代码没有任何影响。
It doesn't have any meaning,
it doesn't have any impact to the code.
就是互相帮助，互相帮助才能认出来
Is just to help each other help
folk out to be able to spot
这个函数需要一个新的关键字。
that this function needs a new keyword.
这显然是需要改进的地方。
That is clearly something that
probably needed to be improved.
这就是解决方案4的用武之地。
And that is where solution 4 came in.
我们必须首先提倡我们知道它需要新的功能之一
We had to advocate first one of
the functions we know it requires new
我们研究过的关键词。
keywords we've worked.
这就是解决方案4出现的地方。
And that's where solution 4 came along.
布糖。
The cloth syntactic sugar.
但它是一种语法糖。
But it is a syntactic sugar.
这意味着一些东西可以改变它的外观，但是
That means something that
changes the way it looks, but
也改变不了什么。
doesn't change it under the hood.
为了我们的目的，为了这一点，我们将要使用它在这里的方式,
For our purposes, for this bit here,
the way we're going to use it here,
这改变不了什么。
it doesn't change anything under the hood.
有两个因素促成了这一结果。
Two things motivate this.
它出现在2015年，ES6，在宣布
It came along in the year 2015,
ES6, In declaring
我们的功能用户创建器，当执行时
our function user creator, when executed
使用新的关键字 help 自动返回一个对象到 user1。
automatically with the new keywords
help returns out an object into user1.
再次运行它会将一个对象返回到 user2，这里有两个重要的部分。
Run it again will return an object into
user2, there's two important parts to it.
这是自动生成对象的函数。
There's the function that produces
the object automatically.
然后还有共享的函数存储。
And then there's the shared
store of functions.
它们都捆绑在同一个功能对象组合上。
They're all bundled up on
the same functional object combo.
但是我们向 JavaScript 分别宣布了这两个部分。
But we announced to JavaScript
the two parts separately.
我们声明用户创建器，它创建一个函数，然后
We declare user creator,
that creates a function and
一个有原型属性的对象和一个对象。
an object with a prototype property
on it with an object to it.
我们可以完全独立地存储这些功能。
Which we can store then totally,
independently, the functions.
在其他语言中，这两件事是紧密相连的，对吗？
In other languages, these two things are
so kind of intimately connected, right?
这是有意义的，这个函数运行时创建一个对象，返回它,
It makes sense, this function when it
runs creates an object, returns it out,
这个对象可以访问这些函数。
and that object has access
to these functions.
所以它们就像是紧密相连的。
So they're like intimately connected.
在其他语言中。
In other languages you.
即使在 JavaScript 中，它们也是紧密相连的
Even in JavaScript,
they're intimately connected and
他们用的是同一个功能性物体组合。
they're on the same
functional object combo.
但是在其他语言中，你可以一起声明它们。
But in other languages you
can declare them together.
知道在运行时声明的函数返回一个对象的访问权限
Know declaring the function who when run
returns out an object that has access to
完全分开申报。
totally separately declared.
在项目属性中出售的原型对象中的函数,
The functions that go into the prototype
object sold on the project property,
对不起，项目属性上的对象，所有的函数对象组合。
sorry that the objects on the project
property, all that function object combo.
所以是的，它们存放在一起,
So yes, they are stored together,
但是它们没有被声明，这意味着我们不会一起将它们编写到 JavaScript 中。
but they're not declared that means we
don't write them to JavaScript together.
我们不会同时写作业说明来实现这两个目标。
We don't write the instructions of jobs
to achieve those two things together.
我们不把它们写在一起，我们分开运行。
We don't write them together,
we run separately.
另一种语言是我们在一个结构中一次完成所有的工作,
Another language is we do that all
in one construct, in all in one go,
都是一种格式。
all in one format.
这种格式的人，任何人都知道这个构造叫什么
And that format people,
anyone know what that construct's called
能让我们一起做这些同时保存这些 Peter？
that allows us to do these together,
save these at the same time, Peter?
亚当: 一个子句。
&gt;&gt; Adam: A clause.
威尔 · 句子: 一个确切的子句。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: A clause exactly.
是宣读从句，彼得。
It's pronounced clause, Peter.
亚当: 对不起。
&gt;&gt; Adam: Sorry.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 这是个玩笑，显然是个玩笑，一个确切的条款，我们开始吧。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: That's a joke, obviously
joke, a clause exactly, there we go.
但是彼得，你是那么的善良，有人指出你不是。
But Peter, you're so
kind that you were pointed out you do not.
你真的是一个非常非常好的人。
You truly in a very, very nice person.
不像我，所以我们写我分享的方法,
Unclearly unlike myself, so
we're writing I shared methods,
这些方法被所有人共享。
these methods that get
shared by all others.
实际上，让我们只是帮助自己在这里有一个用户701,
Actually let's just to help
ourselves out here have a user 701,
再次运行用户创建器就会出现这种情况,
which would have come out of
running user creator again,
我们还是在这里做吧，以防万一,
let's actually do it here just in case,
用户701，另一个调用用户 Creator 的结果。
user 701 with a result of
another call to user Creator.
让我们假设 Sarah 和19岁，以及在前面的新的关键词
Let's say with Sarah and 19 and
the new key word of course in front and
会返回到用户701。
that would have returned
out into user 701.
这次让我们把这个问题解决，得到这个对象
And this time let's get this right,
have the object
原始财产达到
with the proto property up to
共享对象的名字 Sarah,
the shared object and then name, Sarah,
19分。
score 19.
每个人都能得到这部分，我希望这不会让人。
Everyone gets this portion here,
I hope that's not throwing people.
这两个对象，它们都可以访问这些共享的函数、方法。
Those two objects, they both have access
to these shared functions, methods.
我们把它们保存在同一个功能组合中，但是
We're saving them on the same
functional combo, but
我们正在宣布他们，威尔 · 森塔斯: 分开。
we're declaring them,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Separately.
让我们在一个地方做这一切。
Let's do it all in one place.
类的结构让我们可以做到这一点。
And the class construct lets us do that.
在这里，它是句法甜言蜜语，我实际上要直接到这里。
Here it is, it's syntactic sugar folk,
I'm actually going to go straight to here.
这是我们之前做的两部分，对吗？
These were the two parts we did before,
right?
记住，我们创建了函数用户,
Remember, we got our
function user created,
创建一个函数对象组合。
which creates a function object combo.
虽然当它运行的时候会在内部创建一个新的关键字,
Though when it's run Will create
inside of itself with a new keyword,
一个对象首次存储 user1，存储 user701,
an object storing user1 first time,
storing user 701,
第701次每个人都可以访问这个充满功能的对象。
701st time that each have access
to this object full of functions.
用户创建器.prototype.increment。
User creator.prototype.increment.
用户创建者.prototype.login。
User creator.prototype.login.
我们在那里拯救他们。
We save them there.
现在一切都没有改变。
Now nothing has changed under the hood.
我们只需要做这两个单独的声明或者分配
We just get to do these two separate
declarations or assignments
在一个结构中，我们称之为类。
in one construct, we call it a class.
我们接受函数的标签，我们让你接受类的标签。
We take the label of the function and
we make you the label of the class.
一旦你宣布一个类，我们认为我们得到了什么人？
As soon as you declare a class,
what do we think we get people?
威尔 · 森特斯: 丹 阿丹: 一个物体。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Dan?
&gt;&gt; Dan: An object.
我们得到了一个函数对象组合。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: We get
a function object combo.
威尔 · 森特斯: 我们得到一个物体，是的。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: We get an object, yes.
我们得到一个准备好接收函数和对象的对象。
We get an object ready to receive
a function and an object.
一旦我们做到了，我们就要处理里面的第一个部分。
As soon as we do it we're gonna
deal with the first bit inside it.
所以一旦我们声明它，我们就会得到一个函数对象组合。
So as soon as we declare it,
we get a functional object combo.
如果没有，我们有一个函数对象组合。
If not,
we've got a functional object combo.
函数对象组合的第一位，我们给出了字幕构造函数,
And the first bit of the function object
combo, we give the subtitle constructor,
这是函数位，也就是函数对象组合。
and that's the function bit, or
the function object combo there it is.
我们不知道。
We don't know.
我们给它一个副标题，构造函数。
We give it a subtitle, constructor.
Will Sentance: 当然，它是在函数对象组合中出现的
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: And of course it gets
on it in the function object combo in
对象位，一个原型属性，它是一个充满函数的对象,
the object bit, a prototype property,
which is an object full of function,
还没有，我们应该立即储存什么
well not yet,
what do we immediately store though, and
我们不再手动分配他们看，我们只是列出了他们。
no longer do we manually have to assign
them look we just list them out.
中间甚至没有逗号，我们只是把它们列出来。
Not even commas in between,
we just list them out.
我们想列多少就列多少，他们都会一个接一个地被带走
We can list as many out as we want and
they're all gonna be taken one by one and
在幕后，JavaScript 在运行什么？
behind the scenes what's
JavaScript running?
它会显示用户创建者.prototype.increment 和
It saying user
creator.prototype.increment, and
它把它们刺进了那个物体。
it's sticking them into that object.
伙计们，这里什么都没有改变。
People, nothing has changed
under the hood here.
在通过声明一个函数来声明一个类之前，我们已经声明了它。
We have as soon as we declare a class
before we did it by declaring a function.
它隐式创建了一个附加到它的对象，一个函数对象组合
Which implicitly created an object
attached to it a function object combo
其中有一个原型属性，这是一个对象本身。
into which had a prototype property
which was an object itself.
存储我们共享的函数。
Into which we stored our shared functions.
现在，我们创建一个子句，它是一个函数对象组合。
Now, we create a clause which
is a function object combo.
第一部分，我们给出一个字幕构造函数
And the first bit of it,
we give a subtitle constructor and
你可以看到它们是一样的。
you can see it's identical.
我们传递给另一个构造函数的第一件事情是在您的路径中，对不起。
在您的路径中，我们首先传递给另一个构造函数的第一件事，对不起。
That first thing we pass into this other
constructor first in your path, sorry.
我们首先要存放在里面。
我们首先要储存在里面。
First thing we store in it.
给自己一个构造函数是函数对象组合的函数位。
And give ourselves a constructor is the
function bit of the function object combo.
下面列出的所有函数,
And then all the functions
we list out below,
我们只是按名字把他们列出来。
we're just gonna literally
list them out by name.
在幕后，乔治，我们采取的第一个和
Behind the scenes George,
we're taking the first one and
我们上去，然后我们去函数对象组合，那就是类。
we're going up, off we go to our
function object combo that is the class.
看看它的对象位，看看它的原型属性和
And look on the object bit of it and
look on its prototype property and
看看这个对象和故事方法，叫做 increment。
look at that object and
story method, called increment.
然后下一张幻灯片是登录。
And then the next slide it goes login.
然后我们去一个用户创建类,
我们去一个用户创建类,
Off we go to a user creator class,
它实际上只是一个函数对象组合，看看原型属性。
which is really just a function object
combo and look on the prototype property.
我们在它上面插入一个登录属性并分配一个函数。
We insert a login property on it and
assign a function.
之后就是一样的了。
之后就一样了。
And after that it's the same.
当我们运行 user create 时，我在这里做了大写，没有改变。
当我们运行用户创建，我已经做了大写在这里没有改变。
When we run user creates I've done
the upper case here no change.
当我们用关键字运行 user creator 时，知道我们运行函数的哪个位
When we run user creator with the key word
knew which bit do we run of the function
对象组合，丹？
object combo, Dan?
当我们运行前面带有关键字 new 的9的 user creator 时,
When we run user creator with either a
nine with the keyword new in front of it,
我们运行函数对象组合的哪一部分。
which bit of the function
object combo do we run.
丹: 构造函数。
阿丹: 构造函数。
&gt;&gt; Dan: The constructor.
这个函数，是的，我们现在叫它构造函数，但是
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: The function,
yeah we call it constructor now but
其实功能是一样的。
it's really just the same function, yeah.
当 out 从中返回一个物体,
And when out returns from it an object,
它会链接到函数对象组合的哪一部分，丹？
it's gonna link to which bit of
the function object combo Dan?
丹: 原型。
&gt;&gt; Dan: The prototype.
确切地说，原型对象，什么都没有改变。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Prototype object
exactly, nothing has changed.
但是它看起来确实更像其他语言。
But it does look a lot
more like other languages.
但对我来说我不知道,
But that to me, I don't even know,
因为它和其他语言一样吗？
because is it doing what other
languages are doing under the hood?
不，绝对不是。
No, it's definitely not.
这几乎是更多，我不知道，它再次使更清晰。
And that's almost more, I don't know,
it makes again more legible.
这使得它显然更具可读性。
It makes it more apparently readable.
但在幕后，什么都没有改变。
But behind the scenes, nothing's changed.
意思是如果我们想真正理解和调试
Meaning if we wanna really understand and
debug and
使用这些技术，会更有针对性
use these techniques,
it's even more pertinent
我们现在知道引擎盖下面发生了什么。
that we now understand what's
going on under the hood.
因为现在它看起来更像其他语言了。
Going on under the hood because even
more now it looks like other languages.
意义将带来我们对其他语言如何实现的所有观点
Meaning will bring all our views of
how those other languages implement
这些功能，但不是做在现实生活的幕后。
these features, but ain't doing
in real life behind the scenes.
顺便说一下，这是完全相同的模型，正如我们所看到的，回到解2。
It's exactly the same model by the way,
as we saw all the way back and solution 2.
它刚刚被自动化包装，新的关键井,
It's just been wrapped by
the automation the new key well,
很多代码都被新的关键词自动化了。
it's a lot of the codes been
automated by the new key word.
现在完成了我们函数起始点的设置
And now wrapped the setting up of
our starting point of our function
当 run 返回对象时。
which when run returns out objects.
并且有行为丢失的物体现在有权使用那里的股份或功能,
并且有行为丢失的物体有权使用那里的股份或者功能,
And has act lose objects have access
to the shares or functions there now,
我们现在通过一次性设置的过程，在类构造中,
we now through the process of setting this
up in one go In the class constructs,
在教室里。
in the class setup.
但是这并没有改变什么，它只是让我们写更少的代码。
但是它并没有改变任何事情，它只是让我们写更少的代码。
But it ain't changing anything under the
hood, it just makes us write less code.
这就是所谓的语法糖让它看起来更漂亮,
It's what's called a syntactic sugar,
makes it look prettier,
我猜这就像蛋糕上的糖霜，我不知道。
I'm assuming it's like icing
sugar on a cake, I have no idea.
从语法上来说，你就像，让它看起来更漂亮，但是
Syntactically you're like,
makes it look prettier, but
这改变不了什么。
it ain't changing anything under the hood.
好了，各位，利益无疑将成为一个新的标准
All right folk, benefits emerging
as a new standard no doubt
感觉更像是其他语言 Python 和 Java 的开始。
feels more like the start of
other languages Python and Java.
它看起来很像其他语言、语言、问题的风格。
It looks a lot like the style of
other languages, languages, problems.
我说95是解决方案3,99% 的开发人员不知道它是如何工作的。
I say 95 for solution 3, 99% of
developers have no idea how it works.
再问一次，为什么是失败面试？
Again, why it's fail interviews?
我不知道这是一个非常但是
I don't know this is a very but
不能解决他们想要解决的问题。
can't solve the problems that they want
to solve the way they want to solve them.
但你不会成为那些人中的一员。
But you will not be one of those people.